“Grandpa, if it doesn’t
work this time, I
don't know what I’ll
do without you” The
granddaughter said through heavy
tears.
“It will work.
Me and him have
a deal.
He never breaks a
deal” The grandfather tried
to say this soothingly
to his granddaughter but
lapses of shaky fear
made its way through
with each pause of
the sentence.
She broke down sobbing
and laid her head
against the scratchy, dark
brown, wool blanket her
grandfather had draped over
his body while he
lay back against a
mountain of pillows.
There was an in-home
heart monitor that sat
next to the small
twin sized mattress her
grandfather had against the
far wall of his
small room, the room
being just long enough
to accommodate the length
of his bed.
The grandfather's hands had
become so frail, a
once powerful chin and
strong cheekbones sat wrinkled
and withered with age
and sickness.
His hair at a
time had such length
to it, hanging at
least a foot past
his shoulders, silky jet
black with almost streaks
of brown that ran
through thick curls.
There was almost nothing
left of his hair.
The granddaughter almost couldn’t
recognize those deep and
sunken eyes.
“Bring it here” The
grandfather said shakily.
Without question the granddaughter
left the room hurriedly.
Five minutes later she
returned with a basket
that had a cloth
over the top of
it.
She set it down
on her grandfather's lap
and then sat down
herself with her face
in her hands.
The grandfather grabbed a
large knife from the
small bedside table, raising
it above the basket
with both hands with
the point facing straight
down.
The sound of a
child crying sounded from
the basket and the
granddaughter walked over to
the wall, facing it
with her face still
in her hands sobbing
hysterically.
“It’ll be okay dear.
Your mother had to
do this once too,
I only ever ask
once.
Thank you for your
sacrifice.” With those words
the grandfather plunged the
knife into the basket.
The child's crying stopped.
A soft whisper sounded
through the room.
"Another measly 40 years
old man… "