Are you looking for
a powerful and eco-friendly
PC that can help
you get your work
done faster and more
efficiently?
Look no further than
the Acer Aspire Vero
AV15-51-7617 Green PC!
This PC is not
only designed to pack
a punch with the
11th Gen Intel Core
i7-1195G7 and Intel Iris
Xe Graphics, but it
also comes with PCR
materials and a Vero-Sleeve
to help reduce its
environmental impact.
If that isn't enough
to convince you, this
PC also boasts a
stunning 15.6" FHD IPS
100% sRGB-Display that's easy
on your eyes and
lets you work or
watch your favorite movies
without worrying about screen
glare or eye strain.
And with the added
bonus of Wi-Fi 6,
you can easily connect
to the internet and
stream all your favorite
content without buffering.
Upgrade your home office
setup or take it
to the next level
in school with the
Acer Aspire Vero AV
15-51-7617 Green PC.
You won't regret it!